itoris.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy

## General statement

We guarantee that your privacy is respected. The policy describes how your private data might be collected, kept and used as well as important notices connected to it. Please make sure you accept the privacy policy of IToris when you use this website.

## Collection and Usage of Information

Your personal information (name, address, telephone number, company name) is provided by you on a voluntary basis only. This information will be used in your request only (e.g. when you need an invoice).

Technical information (your IP address, browser version) is collected for inner purposes only so that to improve technical performance of our website thus making your use of it to become more convenient.

Your email address will be used for communication purposes as well as login to our website when your new account is generated.   
We never share your personal information with anyone else.

We never collect your payment secure information (credit card or other payment information). It is collected on the side of the authorized payment gateway [2CheckOut](http://www.2checkout.com/).

## Information keeping

Information collected is kept securely. The access to the information is provided only to the authorized employees who have signed the non-disclosure agreements with IToris.

## Other important notices

In order to identify your presence on our website special technical means called “cookies” are used. Cookies are special data that is sent from our website to your browser to keep your session and recognize you during your next visit. If you feel this to be unsecure please change your browser’s configuration in such a way so that to refuse receiving cookies.

When required by law it may be necessary to release your personal information to the authorized state representatives.

This privacy policy is subject to change at any time. Any changes applied will be immediately reflected on this page.
